(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-26T23:09:37.119862",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ANYA MELFISSA
KOBO KANAERU
MOONA HOSHINOVA
KUREIJI OLLIE
TSUNOMAKI WATAME
TAKANASHI KIARA
NERISSA RAVENCROFT
IIDA POCHI.
弄られて 垂れ流す 音のない音
Toyed with, pouring out soundless sounds,
遍く名前を捨てたのね あなたのモザイクが泣いてる
you've completely cast away your name, haven't you? Your mosaic is weeping.
can not, can not, not, not, not deny
紛れもなく真実
Unmistakably the truth.
さあ 預けて 回帰するように
Come, surrender it, as if returning to the source.
エネルギーはサイクル そう いまは
Energy is a cycle, yes, right now...
無重力 象徴的なパレード
Weightlessness, a symbolic parade.
この月夜に 仰げよ仰げ
On this moonlit night, look up, look up.
completeness
鳴呼 命の灯を掲げ
Ah, raise high the flame of life.
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., 欺いて
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., deceive them.
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., 抱きしめて
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., embrace me.
ねえ 無防備だね
Hey, you're defenseless, aren't you?
美しい戯れに
In this beautiful play,
人は壊れてゆく
people break down.
可笑しいわね
How comical, isn't it?
'cuz we're all alone
噛み締めてもまだ痛むなら
If it still hurts even when you grit your teeth,
手を挙げ 希え
raise your hands and pray.
oh, when you bleed, 惑星にそう
Oh, when you bleed, across the planet,
その影を伸ばせ
cast that shadow far.
ねえ 私の世界が 知りたがっているわ さあ
Hey, my world wants to know... come on.
you bleed, yes, bleed その血で
You bleed, yes, bleed, with that blood,
天の五線譜を書き換えれば
if we rewrite the heavenly musical staff,
code 'KiLLKiSS' uh...
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., 欺いて
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., deceive them.
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., 抱きしめて
KiLLKiSS judy.., KiLLKiSS jude.., KiLLKiSS juda.., embrace me.
ねえ あからさまね
Hey, how blatant.
醜い終局に
Toward an ugly endgame,
すべてが変わってゆく
everything is changing.
儚いのね
How fleeting.
そう このまま
Yes, just like this,
壊れて
breaking apart...
Lari lari la la lari da
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY 細胞 LEVEL
BREAK AWAY BREAK AWAY, down to the cellular level.
割に不本意 現状維持で立ってる姿 仕草
Rather reluctant, standing there maintaining status quo, those gestures
滑稽でしょう DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
are comical, aren't they? DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
I'M SO LAZY 多分そう
I'M SO LAZY, probably so.
FINE SOUND 並べてるだけの人 TRASH
FINE SOUND, people just lining them up, TRASH.
TRASH TOSS AWAY DON'T YOU THINK? DON'T YOU THINK?
IN THIS WORLD この頭には
IN THIS WORLD, inside this head,
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL 舞い散る花びら
WHAT A BEAUTIFUL sight, fluttering flower petals.
バラライカ 飲みたいな
I'd like to drink a Balalaika.
Lari lari la la lari da
誰もが Night Out
Everyone's having a night out.
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON
RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON RIDE ON a moment's emotion.
心は 95
My heart rate is 95.
狂気の SAMURAI
A samurai of madness.
血走らせた目で
With bloodshot eyes,
引くくらい READY TO DIE
almost shockingly READY TO DIE.
陽は昇り
The sun rises.
あなたの空 真っ黒な SORA
Your sky, a pitch-black sky,
荒々しく引きちぎって
tear it apart violently.
ほら その場所で
Look, right in that place,
聞こえてくる 鼓動の仕掛け
the mechanism of pulsating heartbeats you hear,
轟くのは
what roars out
誰かのじゃない 己の調べ
is not someone else's, but your own melody.
目の前に広がる
The world spreading out before me
世界はブルー
is blue.
ひとまず
For now,
さあ move, move
come on, move, move,
speak about 生き方
speak about how to live,
there's no need
何をそんなに張り切って偉そうに
Why are you working so hard and acting so mighty?
Ah give me more 愛を
Ah, give me more love,
右も左も知りはしないで笑いな
without even knowing left or right, don't laugh.
Don't you think? Don't you think?
ニヤリ影が笑う
A smirking shadow laughs.
世界は大概
The world is mostly
C-R-A-Z-Y
繰り返すように ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
As if repeating, ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on.
わかってはいない
You don't even understand,
アレコレ authorize
authorizing this and that.
tell me something for the new
時代のバイブル
bible of the era.
clap back
losin' my mind shooting my side
save it あなたのその瞬間
save it, that moment of yours.
maybe nothing wrong, nothing wrong
La-dee-la-lee-la-la la-lee-la
誰もが大体
Everyone is mostly
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
Ride on an instant emotion, ride on, ride on...
心は95
My heart is at 95,
狂気のサムライ
a samurai of madness.
血走らせた目で引くくらい ready to die
With bloodshot eyes ready to die.
ハロー 日は昇り
Hello, the sun rises,
あなたの空 真っ黒な空
your sky, pitch-black sky,
荒々しく引き千切って
tear it violently apart.
ほら その場所で
Look, in that place,
聞こえてくる鼓動の仕掛け
the trick of the beating heart you hear.
驚くのは まだこれから まだこれから
It's too early to be surprised, it's just beginning.
あぁ もう待ちわびて
Ah, I'm already tired of waiting,
時計の針 零時の街
the clock hands, midnight city.
猛々しく
Fiercely,
raise your voice
ほら すぐそこで
Look, right over there,
始まり出す孤高の宴
the solitary banquet begins.
奏でるのは己の調べ
What is being played is one's own melody,
唯一無二の己の調べ
the one-and-only melody of oneself.
わーい！
Yay!
Para Hatiyan, sang Putri Merak yang tertiup angin... Aku Pavolia Reine dari Hololive ID!
To all Hatiyans, the Peacock Princess... I am Pavolia Reine from Hololive ID!
Attention please, I'm Reine from Hololive ID Generation 2!
皆様ご機嫌よう、私ホロライブインドネシア2期生パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの。
How do you do, everyone? I am Pavolia Reine from Hololive Indonesia 2nd Generation.
And welcome to Pavolia Reine's Peacock of the Blue Flame!
Yay! Pavolia Reine's 2025 Birthday! Welcome!
イエーイ、ようこそ！
Yay, welcome!
えっと、左上にハッシュタグがありまして...
Um, there is a hashtag on the upper left corner...
There's a hashtag on the upper left corner. It reads #ReineMEPtember2025,
which is pretty much the same hashtag I've been using for the past few years, yeah.
And if you guys have any thoughts throughout the live, anything,
you can write it and I'll be looking forward to them.
ご感想 and everything you guys can write.
Your impressions and everything, you guys can write them.
Campur-campur deh ngomongnya, waduh. Ya gitu deh pokoknya.
My speech is so mixed up, oh boy. Well, anyways!
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live. You don't have to write it now, 今じゃなくても大丈夫です。
I'm excited to know what you guys think of the live. You don't have to write it now, it's fine if it's not right now.
But I will be waiting. Yeah, so just put any of your thoughts in the hashtag, okay?
And next, I want to talk about the concept of the stage.
Look at this! It's so cool, right?
There's a mysterious flame, mysterious locks, mysterious cans, mysterious...
Where's the liquid? Well, there was like a blue liquid there, but I mean, you saw it, right? Yeah!
If you... I guess if you think of fire or flame, you know,
usually you guys think of the color red, right, automatically? 火と言えばですね、
usually you guys think of the color red, right, automatically? Speaking of fire,
赤のイメージが強いかもしれませんが...
you might have a strong image of red, but...
but actually, the blue flame is the strongest, ya enggak sih?
but actually, the blue flame is the strongest, right?
But actually, 実はですね、青い炎が一番強い...と思います。
But actually, truth be told, I think the blue flame is the strongest.
Yeah, so that's the theme of today's birthday!
I want to show you guys just how hot a blue flame can be through hot songs,
and songs that will make you feel Ada yang seru banget, so 熱い, so... huff, gitu.
and songs that will make you feel super excited, so hot, like... phew! You know.
Pokoknya, just look forward to it, okay?
Anyway, just look forward to it, okay?
And the songs you've seen today, we have two songs. The first one was QILQKISS,
そうですね、すごく好きなあべむじか様の'QILQKISS'です。
yes, it was Ave Mujica's "KiLLKiSS," a song I really love.
And then 2曲目は、私がすごい大好きなプロセカのユニットVivid BAD SQUAD様の'CR詠ZY'でした。
And the second song was "CR詠ZY" by Vivid BAD SQUAD from Project Sekai, a unit I really love.
And the second song was CR詠ZY from a unit I really, really like from ProSeka, Vivid BAD SQUAD. I hope you guys enjoyed it!
イエーイ！
Yay!
Ya memang kalau Reine tuh suka banget gitu sama lagunya, hehe.
Reine really loves those songs, hehe.
Jadi masih akan ada lebih banyak lagi. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs,
So there's going to be even more. There's gonna be way more, more, more, more songs,
and I'm sure there's a lot of guests! I hope you guys are excited for them.
そう、これからもね、もっともっと熱くなるからね、ゲストも many many many many many! So please look forward to it!
That's right, it's going to get hotter and hotter from here on out, and there are many, many guests! So please look forward to it!
But for now,
I'm gonna sing
one of my original songs.
Do you guys know what it is?
The next song is...
Love Me Love Me!
ずっとキミのとなりじっと
Always right beside you,
見てるばかり アイアイ
I just stare intently at you.
やまない雨 世界に
In a world with ceaseless rain,
2人きり 永遠
just the two of us, for eternity.
刻むように 心臓
As if engraving it, my heart,
今 この手に
right now, in these hands.
痛みさえも愛のカタチ
Even pain is a form of love.
運命に結ばれた小指を握る
I hold the pinky finger tied by fate.
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
Love Me Love Me
ワタシシカイラナイ
You need no one but me.
Love Me Love Me
キミガイラナイ
I need no one but you.
ぎゅっと抱きしめたら
If I hold you tight,
きっと逃げられない
I'm sure you can't escape.
チクタク針が回る
The tick-tock clock hands spin
世界に2人きり
in a world with just the two of us.
現実壊すように
As if destroying reality,
感情押し殺して
smothering my emotions.
どんな悲鳴さえも
Even any scream is
愛のメロディー
a melody of love.
運命に結ばれた小指を握る
I hold the pinky finger tied by fate.
約束をしよう
Let's make a promise.
Love Me Love Me
ワタシシカイラナイ
You need no one but me.
Love Me Love Me
キミガイラナイ
I need no one but you.
あー愛して
Ah, love me,
あー愛され
Ah, be loved,
離れられない you and me
inseparable, you and me.
2人きりでいい
Just the two of us is fine.
Give me your love
願うほど滴る赤い色
The red color dripping the more I wish,
何かも染めてしまう愛を
love that stains everything,
もっと頂戴
give me more.
ワタシシカイラナイ
You need no one but me.
Love Me Love Me
キミガイラナイ
I need no one but you.
Love Me Love Me
ダーダダダダダダダダダダダダダ
Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da
まぁこんなもんでいいか
Well, is this good enough?
はぁそろそろヤメにしよーや
Sigh, let me call it quits soon.
手に入れた無理 それを大事にすんのがお前の売り
Doing the impossible you achieved, holding onto it is your strength.
いつ来る後悔を消せるかは今の自分次第
Whether you can erase future regrets depends on your current self.
やるだけやったれ
Just give it all you've got!
誰かじゃなくて未来の自分に嫌われないように
Not for someone else, but so your future self won't hate you.
比べっちまうの毒毒
Comparing yourself is pure poison.
目の前の壁だけ knock knock
Just knock knock on the wall in front of you.
大そうな理想それで結構
Grand ideals? That's fine.
あとはひたすら前に進むだけ
All that's left is to keep pushing forward!
馬鹿にされればされるほどに
The more they make fun of you,
叶えた時が爽快だろ
the more satisfying it feels when you succeed, right?
まだ行けるはず
I can still keep going.
まだやれるはず
I can still do this.
やっば パラパラ
Whoa, para-para!
ブッかますんだ
Let's smash through!
歌え踊れ騒げつっかビビってんのか?
Sing, dance, make noise—what, are you scared?
やっば パラパラ
Whoa, para-para!
かっとばす場外
Blast it out of the park!
頭で決めた限界なんて
Limits set in your head?
当然一点超突破!!
Breakthrough in one shot, obviously!!
ダダダダダダラ
Da-da-da-da-da-da-ra
いいねその感じ
Nice, I like that vibe.
ダダダダダダラ
Da-da-da-da-da-da-ra
いいエゴの暗示
A great self-suggestion.
最高の景色を見に行くやつ称号
The title for those going to see the best view.
音の鳴る方へ
Toward where the sound leads.
やっば パラパラ
Whoa, para-para!
ブッかますんだ
Let's smash through!
歌え踊れ騒げあがれ まだまだ...
Sing, dance, make noise, get hyped—still not enough!
足りない まだまだ めらめら
Not enough, not yet, burning bright
ガンガンのぼる今何点？
Climbing higher and higher, what's my score now?
ごめん2点3点 ポイント超上
Sorry, 2 or 3 points, way up top.
何があったって俺は俺
No matter what happens, I am who I am.
どんどん進んでる5回目
Moving forward, already on the 5th round.
後悔メールに返信しないで
Don't reply to regretful emails.
今から行くから本番
The main event is starting now.
手拍子 手のひら返しはロマン
Clap along, flipping the palms is romance.
重ねられる努力から散らす火花
Sparks fly from accumulated effort.
Na na na na na na na na na
ヤッパッパッノッパッノッブー かますバンダ
Yappappa noppa nobu, tearing it up, Vanda!
歌え 踊れ 騒げ すかぴ びびってんのか ハッハー
Sing, dance, make noise! Sukapi, are you scared? Haha!
ヤッパッパッノッパッノッブー かっとばせ場外
Yappappa noppa nobu, knock it out of the park!
アタマで決めた限界なんて 当然言ってんのちょっと待った
The limits set by your head? Hold on, what are you saying?
イイリズムの感じ
Feel the good rhythm.
イイ笑顔の暗示
Suggestion of a great smile.
キングに言わす「流石」
Making the king say, "Impressive!"
音の鳴るほうへ
Heading towards where the sound leads.
ヤッパッパッノッパッノッブー かますバンダ
Yappappa noppa nobu, tearing it up, Vanda!
歌え 踊れ 騒げ 上がれ
Sing, dance, go wild, rise up!
まだまだ足りない
Still not enough!
ヤッパッパッノッパッノッブー かますバンダ
Yappappa noppa nobu, tearing it up, Vanda!
段違いのハイブリッド 追いついてハイになれる
A next-level hybrid, catch up and get high!
最高級の宴会日
The highest class party day!
ヤッパッパッノッパッノッブー かっとばせ場外
Yappappa noppa nobu, knock it out of the park!
おタスケマンに言わす「カッカッカッ」
Making Otasukeman say, "Ka-ka-ka!"
バグ爆発する発展 パルプパーティ
Bug-exploding progress, Pulp Party!
イイリズムの感じ
Feel the good rhythm.
イイ笑顔の暗示
Suggestion of a great smile.
キングに言わす「流石」
Making the king say, "Impressive!"
音の鳴るほうへ
Heading towards where the sound leads.
ヤッパッパッノッパッノッブー かますバンダ
Yappappa noppa nobu, tearing it up, Vanda!
歌え 踊れ 騒げ 上がれ まだまだ足りない
Sing, dance, go wild, rise up! Still not enough!
まだまだ めらめら
Still burning bright!
夜の始まりさ
It's the start of the night.
Bunny Girl
誘惑される
Tempted by...
鼓動に
...the heartbeat.
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
To the inner conflict popping away,
愛を乾杯
cheers to love,
伝えられなくても
even if I can't convey it.
恋の始まりさ
It's the beginning of love.
Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
your clear eyes...
孕んで
...bearing them.
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come on, trace those suave steps.
仕事帰りの疲れは
The fatigue from walking home after work,
私と、このグラスに
melt it away with me and this glass.
さあ 自分好みに穿って
Come on, tailor it to your liking.
世間に対する気持ち
Those feelings towards the world,
私に注いでみない？
why not pour them into me?
ありがちなラブソングでも
Even if it's just a cliché love song,
愛が込められてるの
love is filled inside it.
それでも汚れるのね
Yet it still gets tainted, doesn't it?
君を見れば分かるの
Looking at you, I can tell.
下を向く君の目を
Your eyes looking down,
剥ぎ取ろうとはしない
I won't try to strip them away.
だからそんな顔せず
So don't make that kind of face.
手を差し伸べて ほら
Reach out your hand, come on.
夜の始まりさ
It's the start of the night.
Bunny Girl
誘惑される
Tempted by...
鼓動に
...the heartbeat.
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
To the inner conflict popping away,
愛を乾杯
cheers to love,
伝えられなくても
even if I can't convey it.
恋の始まりさ
It's the beginning of love.
Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
your clear eyes...
孕んで
...bearing them.
君の愛を知った気で ハイになっていて
Feeling like I knew your love, getting high,
感度去っていて 毎度泣いていてさ
sensitivity fading, crying every time,
それくらいが良いんでしょう
that much is fine, right?
さあ キザなステップを刻んで
Come on, trace those suave steps.
君の顔色 今ではマシになってきてるから
The shade of your face is looking better now, so...
私をあげるわ
I'll give you myself,
Bunny Girl
誘惑される
Tempted by...
鼓動に
...the heartbeat.
弾け飛ぶ葛藤に
To the inner conflict popping away,
愛を乾杯
cheers to love,
伝えられているはず
it should have reached you.
夜の始まりさ
It's the start of the night.
Bunny Girl
誰かを穿って
Piercing through someone,
澄んだ君の目を
your clear eyes...
孕んで
...bearing them.
ヤミヤミドゥドゥ
Yummy yummy do do
ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do
ヤミヤミドゥドゥ
Yummy yummy do do
ヤミヤミヤミ All night show!
Yami yamu yami All night show!
方針調子？なんだって
Policy, condition? What's that?
徘徊曖昧シャットダウン
Wandering, ambiguous shutdown
傾斜のランウェイ
Inclined runway
逃げ切りワンダー
Escaping wonder
急成長正常難題
Rapid growth, normal dilemma
Moving to 選択肢
Moving to options
引っ込みダーウィンさあ
Introverted Darwin, come on
Won't you steal my heart?
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
衝動現実からの escape のらりくらり SOS
Impulse, escaping from reality, evasive SOS
なら燃え上がるわ全身
Then my whole body burns up
欲張りピープル
Greedy people
Yummy yummy ジャスティス
Yummy yummy justice
One chance 狙う jack pot
One chance targeting the jackpot
願います gabut
Wishing for gabut
のるかそるか kill の
All or nothing, kill or
Look back show!
観戦？歓声？貸せ！貸せ！
Spectating? Cheers? Hand it over!
おすそ分け
Share it with me
Ah ズッキンズッキンパラッパ 冷めないうちに
Ah throbbing, throbbing pa-ra-ppa, before it cools down
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
Ah ズッキンズッキンパラッパ お味はいかが？
Ah throbbing, throbbing pa-ra-ppa, how does it taste?
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
Ah 足りない まだ足りないな
Ah not enough, still not enough
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
Ah Lonely night まだ足りないな
Ah lonely night, still not enough
ビギビギドゥッ ドゥッ
Bigi bigi do do
最高臨界点更新中
Updating the peak critical point
思考のマリアージュ駆け足ドメスティック
Marriage of thoughts, hasty domestic
右か左か逃げるが先だ
Right or left, escaping comes first
暴走中途中 dug dug ガラ空きのダンスホール
Out of control mid-way, dug dug, empty dance hall
卵が先だピースは揃った！
Egg comes first, all pieces assembled!
Sir baby baby baby もう時間がないわ
Sir baby baby baby, there's no time left
ヤミヤムヤミヤミヤムヤミ
Yami yamu yami yami yamu yami
ラリルララルーリ捕まえてルルーラ
Ra-ri-ru-ra-ra-ruu-ri, catch me ru-ruu-ra
壊れる前に
Before I break
Ah ドッキンドッキンパヤッパ ルージュを付けて
Ah throbbing, throbbing pa-ya-ppa, putting on lipstick
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
Ah ドッキンドッキンパヤッパ シンクロニズム
Ah throbbing, throbbing pa-ya-ppa, synchronism
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
Ah Party time まだ足りないわ
Ah party time, it's still not enough
ヤミヤミドゥ ヤミヤミドゥ
Yummy yummy do, yummy yummy do
Ah 範囲外もう消えそうだ
Ah out of range, about to fade away
ビギビギドゥッ ドゥッ
Bigi bigi do do
こっち向いてよ哀・二重
Look over here, sorrowful duplicate
痛いことは嫌いですが
I hate things that hurt, but...
君の手のひらは嫌いじゃない
I don't dislike the palm of your hand.
言葉は飴玉みたいに
Words spread sweetly like candy,
甘く広がってココロ満たす
filling up my heart.
嗚呼 全然分かってない
Ah, you don't understand at all,
永遠に言う通り
always doing as told forever.
完全にフェアじゃない
It's completely unfair...
どこにいても
no matter where I am.
嗚呼「何で？」は効いてない
Ah, asking "Why?" doesn't work.
もっともっとあの子みたいに
I have to become more and more
可愛くならなくちゃ
cute like that girl.
愛情は透明に
Affection becomes transparent,
傷痕は how many?
how many scars are there?
もう体痛いのだって
Even the pain in my body
分かんなくなる
becomes impossible to tell.
延命マタタビ
Life-extending catnip,
週二ご褒美
a reward twice a week.
「もう嫌んくなった」って
So I won't be pushed away,
離されないように
with you saying "I'm sick of you now",
今日だってちゃんと
today as well, I properly do
内緒の毛づくろい
my secret grooming.
にゃんって良い子にするから
I'll be a good cat with a "Meow",
愛して
so love me.
Everybody, today is rubbing day
Get it, get it, this is my courtship
Any, any, any time is fine with me
Gimme, gimme, love me, my darling
会いたいを間違いなんて
Everyone says that wanting to see you
みんなは言う
is a mistake,
取り憑かれているって
that I'm possessed.
ならこの胸で痛く
If so, then what is this painful,
締め付けるような切なさは何なの？
tightening sadness in my chest?
選ぶ言葉
Chosen words,
戸惑う指先
hesitating fingertips,
端正な横顔
a neat profile...
私しか知らない
that only I know.
嗚呼 ランダムご機嫌
Ah, random moods,
もしかして今日は
could today be the day
優しく撫でてくれるのかな？
you'll gently stroke me?
君のソレが
I'm the only one in this whole life
耐えられるのは
who can endure
生涯で私だけなんだよね
that side of yours, right?
あからさまに
Blatantly,
カラダまさに
my body literally
「もう嫌だ」って離れられないよね
can't leave even if I say "I hate this", right?
そうだよね？
Isn't that right?
裏返せばいい
If you turn it inside out,
柑橘の匂い
it smells like citrus fruits.
だって仕草の裏も
Because even behind my gestures,
叶ったって叱られるだけらしい
even if it comes true, I'll just get scolded.
今日だってちゃんとお膝でおとなしく
Even today, I sit quietly on your lap,
ニャンて言わないように
so I don't say "meow",
完全体で
perfectly complete.
「はい喜んで」
"I'll be glad to"
「あなた方のため」
"for all of your sakes."
「はい謹んで」
"Yes, respectfully,"
「あなた方のため」
"for all of your sakes."
差し伸びてきた手
The reaching, helping hand
さながら正義仕立て
is tailored just like justice.
嫌々で生き延びて
Reluctantly surviving,
わからずやに盾
standing as a shield against fools.
「はい喜んであなた方のために」
"I'll be glad to do it for your sakes."
「出来ることなら出来るとこまで」
"If I can help, as far as I can go."
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember the bad things,
奈落音頭奏でろ
play the dance tune of the abyss!
トゥントゥントゥン
Boom, boom, boom!
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take another step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember the bad things,
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
sound out your SOS beat!
トンドンツーツートントン
Dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit!
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(踊れ)
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(もっと鳴らせ)
(Play it louder)
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(踊れ)
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(もっと鳴らせ)
(Play it louder)
慣らせ君の病の町を
Get used to your diseased town,
ドンドン
Boom, boom!
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン
Hide the laughable opinions of others,
ドンドン
Boom, boom!
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを
cast aside those superheroes of justice!
ドンドン
Boom, boom!
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Sound out your SOS beat!
トンドンツーツートントン
Dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit!
怒り抱いても
Even if you hold anger,
優しさが勝つあなたの
your kindness wins out;
欠けたとこが希望
your flawed parts are hope.
Save this game mr.A
Save this game, Mr. A.
救われたのは僕のうちの1人で
The one saved was just one of my selves.
後一歩を踏み出して
Take one more step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember the bad things,
奈落音頭奏でろ
play the dance tune of the abyss!
トゥントゥントゥン
Boom, boom, boom!
もう一歩を踏み出して
Take another step forward,
嫌なこと思い出して
remember the bad things,
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
sound out your SOS beat!
分かれ道思うがままGo To Earth
At the crossroads, go to Earth as you wish.
奏でろハクナマタタの音は
Play the sound of Hakuna Matata!
トントンツーツートントン
Dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit!
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(踊れ)
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(もっと鳴らせ)
(Play it louder)
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(踊れ)
(Dance)
ギリギリダンス
Get it, get it done dance!
(もっと鳴らせ)
(Play it louder)
慣らせ君の病の町を
Get used to your diseased town,
ドンドン
Boom, boom!
隠せ笑える他人のオピニオン
Hide the laughable opinions of others,
ドンドン
Boom, boom!
うっちゃれ正義の超人たちを
cast aside those superheroes of justice!
ドンドン
Boom, boom!
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Sound out your SOS beat!
トントンツーツートントン
Dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit!
「はい喜んであなた方のために」
"I'll be glad to do it for your sakes."
「出来ることなら出来るとこまで」
"If I can help, as far as I can go."
「はい謹んであなた方のために」
"Yes, respectfully, for your sakes."
鳴らせ君の3〜6マス
Sound out your SOS beat!
トントンツーツートントン
Dit-dit-dit, dah-dah-dah, dit-dit-dit!
あらぽちまま〜！
Ara-Pochi Mama~!
読者の皆様こんにちは、お疲れ様です！あらぽちです！
Hello everyone in the audience, thank you for your hard work! I'm Ara-Pochi!
ままに教えてもらった言葉で、お嬢様言葉で自己紹介します。
I'll introduce myself using proper lady-like language that my mama taught me.
皆様ごきげんよう。わたくし、パヴォリア・レイ...
Good day, everyone. I am Pavolia Rei...
ごきげんよう。リセット、リセット。ごきげんよう。わたくし、ホロライブインドネシア2期生、パヴォリア・レイネと申しますの。以後お見知りおきを。
Good day. Reset, reset. Good day. I am Pavolia Reine from Hololive Indonesia Gen 2. Please get to know me well.
パーフェクト！素晴らしいお嬢様でございます！
Perfect! What a wonderful lady!
お嬢様ですね、完全に。お嬢様配信！
You're a total lady, completely. A refined lady stream!
お嬢様ムービング？
Lady-like movements?
お嬢様ムービング！
Lady-like movements!
れいねちゃん！
Reine-chan!
Selamat ulang tahun! Happy birthday! おめでとうー！
Happy birthday! Happy birthday! Congratulations~!
さっきは『Buddy Girl』を一緒に歌いましたー！
Earlier we sang "Buddy Girl" together!
いかがでしたでしょうかー？
How was it, everyone?
どうだった？踊れてた？
How was it? Was I dancing well?
ナイス！もう腰が...
Nice! My back is already...
ノー！マッサージ、マッサージ。肩、肩お願いします、肩。
No! Massage, massage. Shoulders, please massage my shoulders.
あー、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you so much.
私もマッサージが欲しい！
I want a massage too!
はい。お客様凝ってますねー。ここですか？こちらですか？
Sure thing. Customer, you're so stiff. Is it here? Is it this spot?
パーフェクトでございます！どうでしたか？
It is absolute perfection! How was it?
Pochi-mama and Reine! Nova Girl!
何事!? 何事!?
What's going on!? What's going on!?
お嬢様ハイテンションで... 今日も素晴らしいです。さすがです。
Milady is in high spirits... Wonderful as always today. As expected!
Hari ini, today, Pochi-mama... Did you guys see last time Pochi-mama's 3D お披露目?
Today... Did you guys see Pochi-mama's 3D debut last time?
そう、2人で私の3Dお披露目で、レイネちゃんと一緒に歌って踊りました。皆さん見ていただけましたでしょうか？
Yes, the two of us sang and danced together at my 3D debut. Did everyone watch it?
And because of that, today I invited Pochi-mama to dance and sing on stage with me!
ありがとうございます！ 招待していただいてありがとう。
Thank you so much! Thank you for inviting me.
Thank you for coming, I had so much fun! めっちゃ楽しかったね！
Thank you for coming, I had so much fun! It was super fun, wasn't it!
Jadi, apa ya? What should we talk about? If I remember Pochi-mama...
So, what should we talk about? When I think of Pochi-mama...
I remember... お嬢様
I remember... "milady".
Because back then, I thought I'm a princess. So I have to act like a princess.
お嬢様だから、日本語で... I'm an ojou-sama. お嬢様 acting 必要、必要 gitu, guys.
"Because I'm a milady," in Japanese... "I'm an ojou-sama." Acting like an ojou-sama is necessary, guys!
でももう、これでパーフェクトです。さっきの動きで。
But now, you're already perfect with those moves from earlier!
ジャンプで。 こっちの動きですか？
With those jumps! With these moves?
こっちで、こっちでお嬢様。ホロライブIDのお嬢様。
With this, you're an ojou-sama! Hololive ID's ojou-sama!
皆さんもお嬢様になりたい方はね、 チョントしてください。
Everyone who wants to become a milady... Please follow along.
チョントってなんですか？ チョント... チョント apa?
What is "Chonto"? Chonto... What's "chonto"?
真似してください！ こんな動きがお嬢様ですよ！
Please copy us! Movements like this make you a milady!
本当にいいんですかね、これで...
Is this really okay... like this?
ちなみに、ネタバレになると思うんですが、今日の誕生日グッズはね、ポチママが頑張りました！
By the way, I think it might be a spoiler, but today's birthday merch... Pochi-mama worked hard on it!
描かせていただきました！皆さん、ちゃんとグッズ紹介まで最後までしっかり見てくださいね。よろしくお願いいたします！
I was given the opportunity to draw them! Everyone, please watch until the end, including the merch showcase! Thank you!
Pokoknya jangan ke mana-mana, guys. Pokoknya tunggu sampai akhir,
Anyway, she said don't go anywhere, guys. Just wait until the end,
karena ada goods dari Pochi-mama sensei. Kalian pasti tidak mau ketinggalan, kan? Makanya, tonton sampai habis. Oke?
because there's merch by Pochi-mama sensei! You don't want to miss out, right? So watch until the end. Okay?
Thank you Pochi-mama for coming! ありがとうございます！
Thank you Pochi-mama for coming! Thank you so much!
この後もライブが続くので、楽しんでね！
The live concert will continue after this, so enjoy!
教えて！もっと あなたの事
Tell me! More about you
Tell me, more, more, more, tell me, more, more, more
聞かせて！もっと あなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice
Let me hear, more, more, more, let me hear, more, more, more
こんなドキドキ もう抑えきれない
I can't hold back this pounding heart anymore
All I need you, oh! All I need you
友達は卒業 運命の私 見つけてほしいの
Graduating from being friends, I want you to find the fated me
One 勇気を出して
One! Summon up your courage
Two 見つめる作戦
Two! The strategy to stare at you
Three 瞳と目が合えば
Three! When our eyes meet
Fall 止められない
Fall! It can't be stopped
Yeah, yeah, yeah この恋 この愛で Melt, melty 溶けちゃうよ
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this love and affection, melt, melty, I'm gonna melt
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気づいて My darling 届け！大好き！
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling! Reach them! I love you!
アイ (愛) スクリー～ム (Scream) 叫びましょう
Love Scream! Let's shout it out!
(スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！)
(Scream! Ice cream!)
OK! アイ (愛) スクリー～ム (Scream) 叫びましょう
OK! Love Scream! Let's shout it out!
(スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！)
(Scream! Ice cream!)
オリーちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Ollie-chan! Yes! What do you like?
チョコミントよりも あ・な・た！
More than chocolate mint, I like yo-u!
こぼちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Kobo-chan! Yes! What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりも あ・な・た！
More than strawberry flavor, I like yo-u!
レイネちゃん！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Reine-chan! Yes! What do you like?
クッキー＆クリームよりも あ・な・た！
More than cookies & cream, I like yo-u!
みんな！ はーい！ 何が好き？
Everyone! Yes! What do you like?
もちろん 大好き アイ(愛)スクリーム！
Of course, I love Love Scream!
Yeah!
yeah yeah yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this crush, with this love,
melt melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm gonna melt away!
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気付いて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling!
届け！大好き！
Reach them! I love you!
アイ♡スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's shout it out!
お願い 見つけて my darling
Please find me, my darling
お願い 気付いて my darling
Please notice me, my darling
One! 勇気を出して
One! Summoning my courage
Two! 近づく作戦
Two! Operation get closer
Three! 手と手が触れて
Three! Our hands touch
Fall! 止められない
Fall! I can't stop it
yeah yeah yeah この恋 この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this crush, with this love,
melt melty 溶けちゃうよ
Melt, melty, I'm gonna melt away!
ねぇ？ねぇ？ねぇ？気付いて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling!
それは！アナタ！
That is... YOU!
アイ♡スクリーム 叫びましょう
Love, scream! Let's shout it out!
la la la la la love love
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
Because in truth, I'm crazy
白鳥たちはそう 見えないとこでバタ足するんです
Like swans, paddling furiously out of sight
本能に従順 忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct
翻弄も重々承知
Fully aware of life's twists and turns
前途洋々だし... だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
The future is bright... so I take a break now and then
Don't say "lazy"
[Song Title: Don't say "lazy"]
この目でしっかり見定めて
Determining clearly with these eyes,
行き先地図上マークして
Marking my destination on the map.
近道あればそれが王道
If there's a shortcut, that's the royal road.
省ける翼あれば上等
If I have wings to cut corners, all the better!
ヤバッ爪割れた グルーで補修した
Oh no, broke a nail! Fixed it with glue,
それだけでなんか達成感
And just that gives a sense of accomplishment.
大事なのは自分かわいがること
The important thing is to cherish yourself.
自分を愛さなきゃ 他人も愛せない
If you don't love yourself, you can't love others.
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
Because in truth, I'm crazy
能ある鷹はそう 見えないとこにピック隠すんです
A skilled hawk hides its pick out of sight
想像に一生懸命
Giving my all to imagination,
現実絶体絶命
Reality is a dire situation.
発展途中だし... だから不意にピッチ外れるんです
Still a work in progress... so my pitch slips off key
その目に映らないだけだって
It's just that it doesn't catch your eye,
やる気はメーター振り切って
My motivation is maxing out the meter.
いつでも全力で夢見て
Always dreaming at full power,
その分全力で眠って
Sleeping just as hard to match!
ヤリ ちょい痩せた 調子づいて喰った
Did it! Lost a bit of weight, carried away and ate,
それだけでなんで？敗北感
Why do I feel defeated just from that?
すかさずに目標下方修正して
Promptly revising my goals downward,
柔軟に臨機応変 七変化が勝ち
Adapting flexibly, changing form is victory!
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
Because in truth, I'm crazy
孔雀たちはそう...
Peacocks are like that...
誘惑多発だし...
Temptations are everywhere...
だからやけに意志砕けちゃうんです
So my willpower breaks insanely easily.
ヤバ　まさか赤点!?
Crap, am I going to fail!?
いや　ギリクリア!
Nah, I barely passed!
それだけでなんか全能感
That alone gives me a feeling of omnipotence.
大事なのは自分　認めてくこと
What's important is to accept yourself.
自分を許さなきゃ　他人(ひと)も許せない
If you can't forgive yourself, you can't forgive others.
Please don't say "You are lazy"
だって本当は crazy
'Cause I'm actually crazy.
孔雀たちはそう
That's right, peacocks...
見えないとこでバタ足するんです
...are kicking frantically where you can't see.
本能に順従　忠実
Obedient and faithful to instinct,
翻弄も重々承知
fully aware of being tossed around.
前途洋々だし...
The future is bright...
だからたまに休憩しちゃうんです
so that's why I take a break sometimes.
わーい！ Gimana? How was it?
Yay! How was it?
Wasn't the gondola, and the bazooka, and everything, very cool?
Wasn't the gondola, the bazooka, and everything super cool?
We had so many songs, but...
...there's still more!
Here's the long-awaited...
...グッズ紹介！　今回も生誕グッズがあります！
...merch reveal! We have birthday merch this time too!
Yeah, まずはこちらですね！
Yeah, first up is this!
青い炎の孔雀ラバーマット, Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat
"Peafowl of the Blue Flame Rubber Mat"!
Ini seperti yang dijanjikan, ya. Just like how we said earlier, Tsurulina spoiler, made by Pochi-mama!
This is as promised! Just like we spoiled earlier, it's illustrated by Pochi-mama!
So many people missed out on the previous rubber mat/desk mat, and so we have another one!
So many people missed out on the previous rubber mat/desk mat, so we have another one!
And for those of you who already have that rubber mat, well, ini ada lagi. Beda! It's different, yeah!
And for those who already have that rubber mat, well, here's another one! It's different, yeah!
And along with the rubber mat, we have...
...the tapestry! Yay!
Ini kalian tidak tergoreng, ya. Kalian tidak tergoreng. Ya nggak apa-apa, kegoreng dikit, pokoknya keren!
You guys won't get burned here. It's fine if it's a little burnt, anyway it's cool!
Ya, sesuai tema live dari kali ini, we have...
Yeah, matching the theme of this live stream, we have...
青い炎の孔雀タペストリー！　イラストは同じだけど、今回はタペストリーですね！　Pochi-mama作です！　Check outしてね！
The "Peafowl of the Blue Flame Tapestry"! The illustration is the same, but this time it's a tapestry, also made by Pochi-mama! Please check it out!
Dan, selanjutnya adalah yang ini, ya.
And next up is this one!
Lanjutannya, buat kalian yang suka minimalist design...
Moving on, for those of you who like minimalist designs...
...for those of you who like designs that are more minimalistic in nature, we have...
...Blueming Flame Coaster! 咲き誇る青い炎のコースター！ Yes!
...the "Blueming Flame Coaster"! "Blooming Blue Flame Coaster"! Yes!
And pokoknya temanya itu cocok banget sama tapestry-nya dan juga rubber mat-nya yang tadi ya, ilustrasi Pochi-mama.
And basically, the theme matches the tapestry and the rubber mat earlier, illustrated by Pochi-mama!
Jadi mendingan masukkan ke keranjang sekarang juga! え、まだできないの？　まあいっか。
So you'd better add it to your cart right now! Wait, you can't yet? Oh well, no big deal!
And then, next one! さらに、こちら！
And then, next up! Furthermore, this one!
Ada juga, seperti biasa, ada voice!
As usual, we also have a voice pack!
今回はいが寿司が大好きだから, because I love sushi so much, 寿司大好きで...
This time, because I love sushi so much...
... membuat "Secret Sushi Strategy" / シークレット寿司作戦 voice pack!
...I created the "Secret Sushi Strategy" voice pack!
Untuk kalian yang suka sushi juga mungkin, ya. Let's go!
For those of you who like sushi too, maybe! Let's go!
最後にフルセットを購入いただいた方には...
Lastly, for those who purchase the full set...
Buat yang beli full set akan ada 数量限定で直筆メッセージと箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードが付いてきます！
For those buying the full set, in limited quantities, it comes with a postcard featuring a handwritten message and foil-stamped autograph!
Akan ada limited edition postcard yang ada message dan tanda tangan dari Reine juga!
There will be a limited edition postcard with a message and signature from Reine too!
...buat yang beli... え、なんでまたインドネシア語？ For those people who buy the full set, let's go!
...for those who buy... Wait, why Indonesian again? For those people who buy the full set, let's go!
え、通常版は箔押し複製サインとメッセージ入り...
And the regular version comes with a foil-stamped copy autograph and message...
...ポストカードが付いてきます！ Yang beli biasa juga akan ada postcard yang ada message dan sign-nya, ya. Okay!
...postcard! Those buying the regular version will also get a postcard with a message and signature. Okay!
And then, next up, I'm going to introduce...
...my new song! Yes! Well, I don't know...
First time doing this genre,
so I'm a little bit shy.
It's a little bit different from what I usually sing,
so I hope you guys can...
If it could resonate with you guys even for a little, I would be so happy.
こんなジャンルの曲をするの初めてでした。
It was my first time singing a song in this genre.
だからね、ちょっと shy です。
So, you know, I'm a bit shy.
Yeah, well, basically, being placed in a box you don't exactly fit, it sucks, right?
And this is some sort of, you know, it's a song of self-acceptance.
And sometimes your flaws are what makes you you.
And even if you're broken, it's fine.
And no one else's opinions should change that.
とにかく自分をありのままを愛していいよって曲です。
Anyway, it's a song about how it's okay to love yourself just as you are.
じゃあ、これから準備するので待っててね。
Well then, I'm going to prepare now, so please wait for me.
Please wait cause I'm gonna prepare. I got a surprise!
Yeah! Bye-bye!
Attention, please!
Are you somebody looking for a new experience?
Or are you by any chance a MERAKyats who just can't wait for when I'm going to be implementing a certain feature?
Or are you simply wanting to get a head start with flexing using super amazing badges and cute emojis?
Well, you're in luck!
My name is Pavolia Reine, and I'm going to be here explaining briefly what is going on with Pavolia Reine's membership. (That is mine, by the way.)
At The Royaltea, our super advanced magical technology grants you badge flexing rights, which you can constantly show off every time you're here with us.
We also make sure to provide you with utmost care and sense of belonging by granting you a one-of-a-kind experience with cute emojis.
At just the right price, you'll be able to join our exclusive Royaltea parties, which also means membership-exclusive streams,
in which we can have various talks, play games together, and do other miscellaneous member involvements.
Like what, you might ask?
Only one way to find out.
And lastly, safety isn't guaranteed, but it is...
development training in which we aim to build a community of people who like living dangerously.
We welcome everybody with open arms to join The Royaltea.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Wake up, another bloody Monday. Say things I never wanted to say.
Up in arms, who can I please? You? Livin' day by day.
Wake up, another bloody Monday. Rinse and repeat until it's Sunday.
Hold it, so frustrated. Ya know I can't do it no more.
I'll say...
No good, down to the core! Hear you knockin', beatin' down my door!
Yell out, scream and shout, but I'll never change it now.
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you, right?
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear.
I'm just so broken.
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey!
I'll stop me!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
You want me to know what I just don't know.
Mold me in a hurry into him? No.
Little did you know, I'm just me, let it go.
Lock me inside a pin of your perfection, correction.
Tearin' me down, am I what you like now?
Don't tell me what, what to do, what to say, what to think about everything.
But did you ever think...
I'll say...
Good with bein' so bad, what's the issue? I'll screw up again!
Yell out, scream and shout, but I'll never change it now.
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you, right?
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear...
...broken...
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Comfortable and pathetic
I like it that way, get it?
You're brutal, judgmental, it's never that simple, but I still want...
...to meet your harsh criteria
Too bad I'm never gonna...
...I'm never gonna fit!
Oh, no!
1, 2, 3, go!
Yell out, scream and shout
But I'll never change it now
I'm just too much, but not enough to please you, right?
No, I'm never, never gonna...
Your idea of ideals that you're screaming in my ear
I'm just so broken...
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
Hey! Hey!
I'll stop me!
I'll never figure it out!
Hey! Hey!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
FIGURE IT OUT
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Never, never, never gonna figure it out!
PAVOLIA REINE ORIGINAL SONG
Figure it Out - SONG & MV COMING SOON